eventials.com 2009-02-17

# Eventials - The Essential Worldwide Event Center

Last Updated: January 18, 2009

Eventials takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. This policy covers how we treat the information that we collect and receive. Your accessing and continued use of our websites signifies your explicit consent to these terms and conditions of our Privacy Policy. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as our services change and expand. We will notify you of such changes by posting them on our site. All amendments will be automatically effective 30 days after they are posted.

Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, to administer your Membership (together, the “Service”) and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

Personally Identifiable Information.

• When you register with us through the Site and become a Eventials Member, we will ask you for certain personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, your email address and the email address of your contacts, home and business postal addresses, and website URLs. We use your Personal Information to provide the Service and administer your inquiries.   
• We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your profile webpage (e.g., without limitation, company, occupation, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences) (“Non-Identifying Information”).   
• We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries.   
• We may also use your Personal Information to contact you with Eventials newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

Log Data.

When you visit the Site, whether as a Eventials Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “Eventials User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration, to increase our Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs. For example, some of this information is collected so that when you visit the Site again, it will recognize you and serve information appropriate to your interests. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests.

Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by Eventials Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Service and then close your browser. Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

We will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide the Services, when we otherwise have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information.

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

Service Providers.

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications by contacting us at info@eventials.com.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement.

Eventials cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Eventials or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

Business Transfers.

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. In such an event, you will have the opportunity to ask not to receive promotional information following any such change of control.

Security

We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access and disclosure. This includes utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input, and storing your information in encrypted form behind a firewall designed to block access from outside our network.

International Transfer

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Eventials may transfer your Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other websites for news and other information. Our Privacy Policy only applies to the Site and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. You should check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them.

Children’s Information

This Site is not directed to children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us a info@eventials.com. If we become aware that a member is under the age of 13 and has provided us with Personal Information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such information from our files.

Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@eventials.com.
